{
    "subject": "resource/Council_Bluffs,_Iowa",
    "predicate": "ontology/motto",
    "object": "\"Iowa's Spirit\"",
    "human_readable": "The motto of Council Bluffs, Iowa is 'Iowa's Spirit'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9814906120300293,
            "question": "What does the motto 'Iowa's Spirit' suggest about Council Bluffs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.979160487651825,
            "question": "Who might have chosen the motto 'Iowa's Spirit' for Council Bluffs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.969221830368042,
            "question": "What is the motto of Council Bluffs, Iowa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9479643702507019,
            "question": "How does the motto 'Iowa's Spirit' influence tourism in Council Bluffs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8589300513267517,
            "question": "What are some ways the city of Council Bluffs embodies 'Iowa's Spirit'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143245577812195,
            "question": "How does the motto of Council Bluffs compare to mottos of other cities in Iowa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6720357537269592,
            "question": "Does the motto of Council Bluffs reflect the values or culture of its residents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6596599817276001,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with Council Bluffs that might relate to its motto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3832693099975586,
            "question": "Where is Council Bluffs located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04798055440187454,
            "question": "What are some other mottos that capture the essence of different cities or states?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The motto of Council Bluffs, Iowa is 'Iowa's Spirit'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Council Bluffs located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events associated with Council Bluffs that might relate to its motto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the motto of Council Bluffs reflect the values or culture of its residents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2302_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2302/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt, it is mentioned that \"The city officially incorporated itself in January of 1853, and its city motto is 'Iowa's Spirit.'\".\n* This information supports the triple.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the document `4.txt`, the city motto of Council Bluffs, Iowa, is \"Unlike Anywhere Else. On Purpose.\" It does not mention \"Iowa's Spirit\" as the motto. Therefore, the statement that \"The motto of Council Bluffs, Iowa is 'Iowa's Spirit'\" is incorrect based on the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "In the context information provided, the motto of Council Bluffs is actually \"Unlike Anywhere Else. On Purpose,\" as mentioned in section 3: \u201cUn-ness\u201d is the central theme of Council Bluffs\u2019 new image campaign, developed last spring to replace the city\u2019s worn motto of \u201cIowa's Leading Edge.\u201d",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}